thk.com 2012-12-12

# Privacy | [ THK ]

## 1\. THK Personal Information Protection Policy

April 1st, 2005   
THK Co., Ltd.   
President and CEO, Akihiro Teramachi 

Fulfilling our legal and social responsibilities towards protecting personal information is extremely important to our company's activities. In particular, we have a duty of confidentiality and must prevent the provision or disclosure of acquired personal and private information about shareholders, board members, company employees, junior employees, contract employees, temporary employees, employees of outside contractors, customers, or suppliers to any outside party against the intended reasons for use, or without good reason. In order for our company to continue to do business whilst maintaining society's trust, we cannot overlook our responsibility to secure and protect personal information. 

Our company strongly recognizes the importance of appropriately safeguarding personal information held by us. In order for our company to accomplish what is required of it in accordance with our social and legal obligations, we must appropriately hold and safeguard personal information and maintain robust and suitable management of such information used in our business and operations.   
management of such information used in our business and operations. To achieve this, we have specified the personal information privacy policy below as a fundamental principal of our company's management, and are working hard to ensure the information security of personal information. 

1\. As well as complying with the Act concerning Protection of Personal Information (Law No. 57, 2003); the guidelines set down by the Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry (METI) and the Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare; and the Tokyo Municipal Government's Personal Information Protection Act, THK has formulated its own "Personal Information Protection Provisions" in recognition of the importance of protecting the privacy of its employees and other parties. THK strictly adheres to these provisions and revisions and improvements are made on an ongoing basis. 

2\. THK is setting up a personal information protection regime that takes into account the nature and scale of the business conducted by each of its divisions, and handles the collection, use, supply (including outsourcing), disclosure, correction, discontinuance of use and deletion of personal information appropriately in accordance with the designated rules. 

3\. To assure the accuracy and reliability of personal information, THK will put in place safety measures that include information security provisions, and will endeavor to prevent improper access to personal information as well as the loss, destruction, falsification or leakage of personal information. 

## 2.Our web site Privacy Policy

Last updated on August 1st, 2012

### INTRODUCTION/ NOTICE AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS OF PRIVACY POLICY

Your use of our web site constitutes your acceptance of the following terms of our web site Privacy Policy, as amended or revised by us. You should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect through our web site [http://www.thk.com](http://www.thk.com/ "http://www.thk.com") and how we use that information. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or how your personal information may be used or affected by your use of our web site, please contact us at ( [web@thk.co.jp](mailto:web@thk.co.jp)) . 

### THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

You do not have to provide personal information to use this web site. However, certain services which you may subscribe for through this web site may require you to provide personal information, such as your name, address, email address and other contact information. We use such personal information to respond to your inquiries and to send you newsletters. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive mailings from us, please refer to the paragraph below headed 'Opt Out'. In addition, and as is typical of web sites generally, incidental to your use of this web site, our web server may automatically log certain information such as the name of your internet service provider, the IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that you use, the date and time you access our web site, the web site address, if any, from which you linked directly to our web site, the web site address, if any, to which you travel from our web site, and other similar traffic-related information. We may also aggregate information relating to your and other visitors' traffic patterns. We use the foregoing information to help us improve our web site and the services that we provide through the web site. We do not use such data in any way to create or maintain a personal profile of you or to collect personal information from you. Generally, we will not disclose information we collect through your use of our web site to third parties. We reserve the right, however, to provide such information to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform certain web site-related services (e.g., web hosting or maintenance services) on our behalf. We also reserve the right to disclose such information to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect or prosecute criminal offences or attacks on the technical integrity of the web site or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, or safety of THK, the users of the web site, or the public. 

### USE OF COOKIES

This web site may contain pages utilizing a technology called [cookies]. By using [cookies], it is possible to identify a user’s computer, but will not identify or collect the user’s personal information. Most browsers will allow you to turn off [cookies] by changing the preference, however, there is a possibility that you will not be able to use all or a part of our services offered on this web site.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address truncated by the last octet prior to its storage using the “_anonymizeIp()” method) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

You can opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

### OPT OUT

If you no longer wish to receive materials from us or want your personal information removed from THK’s database, please contact us at [web@thk.co.jp](mailto:web@thk.co.jp). Alternatively, when you receive materials from us by e-mail or other communications, you can make use of the "opt out" provision in such communications so that we know that you no longer wish to receive such materials from us. 

### REVISIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY

The Internet and the benefits it offers are evolving rapidly, as are the ways in which people use the Internet and the laws surrounding such use. THK therefore reserves the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time. You can determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised by referring to the "Last Updated" date at the top of this page, or if you send us an e-mail at [web@thk.co.jp](mailto:web@thk.co.jp). 

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect through this web site. We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination sites which you visit.
